Next Preview
Hey there!
We are going to Kyoto for sightseeing now.
This time, COCONUT, a member of the group, can't go with us because of her school.
I would like to bring some accessories with me.
Together?
Maybe it's out of focus.
Maybe not.
We are going to enjoy Kyoto sightseeing with COCONUT-sama!
Let's go!
Bye bye!
Is this right?
It looks like a whale.
Cute!
What do you think?
It's cute.
Do you think it's right?
Isn't it amazing?
Ready, Kyoto!
Yay! I'm there.
First time in Kyoto.
First time? I've never heard of it.
I saw it for the first time.
I've never seen it before.
Uh-huh.
I'm not in.
Manners, Ietet. We'll discuss it when we need to.
Yes, please. - No, no, no.
I'm not in, I'm out.
Now that...
Good day to you.
I'm off
I'm nervous
I'll do my best
I'll pray for you
Okay, I'm off.
Nervous
We'll be waiting for you
We are waiting for you
Please step aside
Please wait for your seat
Tent number 5.
Tent No. 7.
The Buddhist altar, the house, the master builder.
May I start with what's the first thing you said?
Oh, okay.
It says "Kichi Osaka Roku".
Oh no... oh no... oh no... oh no...
Does it mean "great luck"? Here.
Number 6, the first number.
Read from the right.
Oh, I see.
Number 10.
It was Hankichi.
Too bad.
HANKICHI
Fast forward.
Good morning.
Oh, no.
It's a wrestling match.
Everyone's still asleep.
That's fine.
I'll sleep in the morning.
Who doesn't have a blanket?
Shukan
It's morning
It's 6 o'clock
It's already 10 o'clock
the end of the week
Hey, Shukan
He won't wake up.
Ashira?
Almost there! Almost there!
8:30!
Good morning, sweetie.
Good night.
I'm up.
Around the usual time.
Next notice